http://www.gospel.com/legal/privacy/#h3

The Gospel
Search:
Effective as of December 2008
Gospel.com (the "Web Site") is owned and operated by The Zondervan Corporation L.L.C. ("Zondervan"), a part of the News America Group, which has adopted a set of Privacy Principles applicable to all its U.S.-based companies. Zondervan has implemented those Principles in this Privacy Policy, which describes how we collect, use and share personally identifiable information ("PII") we obtain from and about individuals located in the U.S. both online and off-line.
All references herein to "Gospel.com" are intended to refer to Zondervan as a whole.
From time to time Gospel.com may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law, our PII collection and use practices, the features of our web sites, or technology. If we make revisions that change the way we collect or use your PII, those changes will be posted in this Privacy Policy and the effective date will be noted at the beginning of this Privacy Policy. Therefore, you should review it periodically so that you are up to date on our most current policies and practices.
If Gospel.com materially changes its practices regarding the collection or use of your PII, your PII will continue to be governed by the Policy under which it was collected unless you have been provided notice of and have not objected to the change.
COLLECTION: COLLECTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION ("PII") BY GOSPEL.COM
General. Gospel.com collects personally identifiable information ("PII" -- that is, information such as your full name, e-mail address, mailing address or telephone number) in order to create or enhance our relationship with you. When we collect PII from you it is because you are voluntarily submitting the information to us in order to participate in activities like surveys, forums, subscription registrations, in connection with content or suggestions you submit to us, chats or bulletin boards, or because you want us to furnish you with products, services or information. We may also obtain PII from reputable third parties.
Cookies. Cookies are small bits of information that the Web Site places on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies remember information about your activities on the site and enable the operator of the site to make your visits to our Web sites more enjoyable.
Gospel.com will
employ cookies to identify you as a unique visitor.
We also may use cookies in a variety of ways, such as allowing for easier logon and relating your use of our web sites to non-personally identifiable information you have provided to us, so that we can track trends, limit the online ads we display to you to those we believe are consistent with your interests and otherwise improve your experience on the Web Site.
We may also use cookies or similar tools to relate your use of our web sites to PII obtained from you or a reputable third party. For example, if you ask us to send you information about our upcoming products or promotions, cookie and/or click stream data about your activities on
the Web Site may allow us to limit the material we send you to the types of items we believe you will find interesting, based upon your activities on our sites and your preferences. However, if we wish to coordinate your personal and web site activity information in this manner, we will obtain your express affirmative consent.
Also, our cookies will not contain PII.
You can program your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being
sent or to refuse cookies completely.
You can also disable our cookies by clicking the "Logout" link on our web sites.
NOTICE: GOSPEL.COM WILL PROVIDE YOU WITH NOTICE ABOUT ITS PII COLLECTION PRACTICES
When you voluntarily provide PII to Gospel.com, we will make sure you are informed about who is collecting the information, how and why the information is being collected and the types of uses we will make of the information.
At the time you provide your PII, Gospel.com will notify you of your options regarding our use of your PII, including whether we will share it with outside companies (See "Choice" below). This Policy describes the types of other companies that may want to send you information about their products and services and therefore may want to share your personal information, provided you have given Gospel.com permission to do so (See "Use" below).
Sometimes we collect personally identifiable information from consumers in manual format or off-line, such as a post card or subscription form. Providing detailed notice in those situations often proves impractical, so consumers will instead be provided with a short notice that describes how to obtain the full text of this Policy and other relevant information from us.
The Web site may be linked to Internet sites operated by
companies other than Zondervan. Some of these third party sites may be co-branded with a Gospel.com or Zondervan logo, even though they are not operated or maintained by Zondervan. The
Web Site may also carry advertisements from other companies. Gospel.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of Web sites operated by third parties that are linked to the Web Site or for the privacy practices of third party or national Internet advertising companies. Once you've left a the Web Site via such a link or by clicking on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party or advertiser site to determine how they will handle any PII they collect from you.
The Web Site may also be linked to sites operated by companies affiliated with Zondervan (i.e., that are part of the News America Group). Although all News America Group entities adhere to the group's Privacy Principles, visitors to those affiliated sites should still refer to their separate privacy policies and practices, which may differ in some respects from this Policy.
CHOICE: GOSPEL.COM WILL PROVIDE YOU WITH CHOICES ABOUT THE USE OF YOUR PII
Gospel.com will not use the PII you provide to us for purposes different from the purpose for which it was submitted, or share your PII with third parties that are not affiliated with Zondervan (i.e., not part of the News America Group), unless we obtain your permission.
USE: GOSPEL.COM'S USE OF PII
Gospel.com will use your PII provided under this Policy in a manner that is consistent with this Policy. If Gospel.com obtains PII from a third party, such as a business partner, our use of that information is governed by this Policy.
Gospel.com may share your PII with companies that are affiliated with us, that is are part of the News America Group of companies. Provided you have given us permission, we may also share your PII with advertisers and business partners that are not affiliated with Zondervan but would like to send you information about their products and services. For example, Gospel.com may offer a newsletter with a co-sponsor that may have special offers or promotions that might be of interest to Gospel.com customers. However, you will always have the opportunity to instruct us not to share your information with third parties when PII is collected. Moreover, we will never share your credit card information with third parties except those Gospel.com uses to perform tasks (such as order fulfillment and payment processing) required to complete purchases you make through the
Web Site.
Gospel.com's employees, agents and contractors must have a legitimate business reason to obtain access to your PII. Gospel.com may share your PII with outside contractors or agents who help us manage our information activities (i.e., sweepstakes administration, order fulfillment, statistical analyses), but they may only use your PII to provide Gospel.com with a specific service and not for any other purpose.
Gospel.com may also enter into agreements with outside companies that possess the technology that allows Gospel.com to customize the advertising and marketing messages you receive on the Web Site.
Your non-PII and click stream data about your activities on the Web Site may be shared with these companies so this customization can be accomplished.
These companies will not share your information with any third party or use it for any other purpose.
Anonymous click stream and demographic information may also be shared with Gospel.com's advertisers and business partners.
There may be instances when Gospel.com may disclose PII without providing you with a choice in order to protect the legal rights of Zondervan, other companies within the News America Group or their employees, agents and contractors; to protect the safety and security of visitors to the Web Site; to protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or to comply with the law or legal process. In addition, if Zondervan sells all or part of its business (such as the Web Site and its related activities) or makes a sale or transfer of assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, Zondervan may transfer your PII to a third party as part of that transaction.
SECURITY: GOSPEL.COM PROTECTS THE SECURITY OF PII
Gospel.com uses reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard PII in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. In addition, we use reasonable methods to make sure that PII is accurate, up-to-date and appropriately complete. Passwords and PII are stored by
Gospel.com behind firewalls.
Credit card information is encrypted both in transit and when stored within Gospel.com's online databases.
ACCESS: HOW TO ACCESS, CORRECT OR DELETE YOUR PII
Gospel.com has implemented a procedure for you to access, correct or delete your PII. If you would like to know the types of information that Gospel.com collects from visitors to the Web Site, please send your request to privacypolicy@gospel.com or write to Legal Department, HarperCollins Publishers, Attention: Privacy Policy, 10 East 53rd Street, New York, NY 10022.
If you would like to know whether Gospel.com has collected PII about you and what PII we have collected, please send us the activities that you participated in on our Web sites which requested PII. After reviewing the relevant databases, we will confirm whether we have collected such information about you and provide a list of your PII on file.
In the event your PII on file is incorrect, you may correct the PII by sending a written request for correction to privacypolicy@gospel.com that includes (1) all of the incorrect PII that you wish to change, (2) the corrected PII and (3) your signature authorizing such changes.
Gospel.com will then correct the PII in our database and send a written confirmation to you.
If you wish to stop all future communications from Gospel.com, please contact privacypolicy@gospel.com, requesting that your PII be permanently removed from any Gospel.com database.
We will send you a written confirmation of such removal.
However, there may be residual information that will remain within our databases that may or may not contain PII. This residual information will not be given to any third party or used for any commercial purpose.
REMEDIES AND COMPLIANCE: HOW TO CONTACT GOSPEL.COM ABOUT PRIVACY CONCERNS
If you have concerns regarding the collection and use of your PII or any other privacy issues, please contact:
Legal Department
HarperCollins Publishers
Attention:
Privacy Policy
10 East 53rd Street
New York, NY 10022
privacypolicy@gospel.com
© Copyright [2009] The Zondervan Corporation L.L.C. All Rights Reserved.
What is the Gospel?
